boilsoft.com 2019-05-08

# Boilsoft Privacy Policy

Your security and privacy is of great importance at Boilsoft, and we persistently spare no effort to protect it.  
When you visit our website, purchase Boilsoft products or when you contact our sales or supporting colleagues, Boilsoft's collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information occurs.

Please pay attention to the following terms to learn more about our privacy policy, including the types of information that are gathered, the purposes of the gathered information and how do we protect your personal information.

**1\. What information do we collect?**

Boilsoft may collect information from you relating to your identity and your personal preferences as they relate to our products. Personal information we may typically collect includes your name, mailing address, email address, telephone number, IP address, even your credit card number, credit card expiration date, etc. Boilsoft will endeavor only to collect such information as it's necessary for the stated purpose. For example, if you purchase Boilsoft products, we will require your name and email so that we can send the registration codes to you and your credit card details to obtain payment. Our objective is to inform you before or at the time of collecting the information and the purposes we use such information for. If we require further information, we will identify the information we wish to collect and the purposes such information is being collected for. If you choose not to provide required information, Boilsoft may not be able to comply with your request or provide certain services.

2\. **What is the purpose for Boilsoft to gather the information?**

Your personal information will help us provide a superior level of customer service. It enables us to give you convenient access to our products and services. In addition, your personal information makes it possible for us to remind you the latest product announcements, software updates, special offers, and events that you might like to hear about.

**3\. How do the 3rd party credit card processors protect customer information?**

Boilsoft software uses secure server hosted by SWREG and other 3rd party credit card processors that encrypt all the customer's personal information including name, address, credit card number credit card expiration date etc. before it is sent to us. Encryption works to prevent any malicious use of your personal information. Your credit card information is only used for online transition. Credit card information in encrypted during the ordering process and is deleted as soon as your order is completed. All other personal information (name, address and product ordered) is held to assist product registration.

**4\. About cookies**

We use "cookies" to better understand what services are valuable to our customers. A cookie is a small text file that a website writes to your hard drive. Cookies work as your identification card and may record passwords, preferences and purchases. Cookies let the web page server know that you have returned to this site. Cookies also can determine other information, such as the daily visitors to our web site and the pages of the site most frequently visited. Cookies are unique and can only be read by the server that assigns them. They cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses.   
 You can change the settings in your browser to prevent cookies if you do not want to have a cookie set when you visit our website. However, by doing so, you may not have full access to all the web pages.

**Opt-in:** By purchasing our products or services, you agree to receive boilsoft newsletter regarding your purchasing products or services.   
**Opt-out:** Users always have the rights to opt out of our newsletters. This option is made available when you click the Unsubscribe here link at the bottom of any newsletter. Or you send us an email telling that you want to unsubscribe to our newsletter
